#### Contact

latifabad hyderabad sindh pakistan 03151303081 (Mobile) hani\_87hyd@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hani-sheikhb13ab593 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Market Research Marketing Strategy Marketing

# hani sheikh

Medical promotion officer at GSK Healthcare Division Hyderabad

#### Summary

Experienced Territory Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the market research industry. Skilled in Analytical Skills, Customer Service, Data Analysis, Marketing Strategy, and Research. Strong sales professional with a Bachelor's of Commerce focused in Business/Commerce, General from University of Sindh.

## Experience

**GSK Consumer Healthcare** Medical promotion officer October 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months) Hyderabad, Sindh, Pakistan

To Promote Principle,s product to Health Care Professionals (HCPs)

Continental Pharmacritual Brussels Belgium **Territory Manager** September 2018 - September 2020 (2 years 1 month) Hyderabad, Pakistan

Date: 1st October 2020

Continental Belgium Pharmaceuticals

Hafiz Muhammad Haris Afzal: Territory Manager

Dear Sir.

I would like to inform you that I am resigning from my position as Territory Manager, effective from 1st October 2020.

Thank you for all the support and opportunities you have provided me over the last few years. I have truly enjoyed my time of working and am very grateful for the encouragement you have given me to pursue my personal and professional goals.

I have to complete my current projects and train other team members to take over my duties. Please let me know if there is anything else I will try to do help my self.

Kindly clear my all dues as soon as possible.

I wish the company continued success for the future and hope to stay in touch. Sincerely,

Hafiz Muhammad Haris Afzal

Don Valley Pharmaceuticals Medical Information Officer January 2016 - August 2018 (2 years 8 months) Hyderabad, Pakistan

### Education

University of Sindh
Bachelor's of Commerce, Business/Commerce, General · (2015 - 2016)

nill